（春野はるのサクラ）ん！
（サクラ）
これじゃ うかつに近づけない
I can't carelessly approach him
like this.
What intense heat and flames.
（チヨ）なんという高熱の炎じゃ
（サクラ）あと １分半
（チヨ）うむ
One and a half minutes left.
Yes.
（サソリ）死ね ババア
Die, Grandma!
（チヨ）ん？
（サクラ）あっ
（チヨ）これでも食らえ
Eat this!
（サソリ）甘いな
You wish!
やはりな　あの戦闘の最中に
チャクラ糸を仕込んでやがったか
Just as I thought.
You attached a Chakra thread
in the middle of that fight, huh?
But the same trick won't work twice!
だが 同じ手が通用するかよ
残念だったな
How unfortunate.
（サクラ）くっ 時間が…
There's no time...
♪～
A voice heard in the distance gives me a hint.
tooku de kikoeru koe wo hinto ni
One by one like-minded people are standing up.
hitori mata hitori tachiagaru doushi
Lets overturn all the everyday, monotonous things.
kurikaesu dake no fudan doori kutsugaesu
I'm ready, are you ready?
junbi iize are you ready
A shiver spreads through my body, violently ringing stomping.
karadajuu furuwasu shindou ni hageshiku uchinarase yo stomping
Constantly stirring in me, it calls me.
taezu tsuki ugokasu call me
Catching that unchanging, never wavering story, Come on!
kawarazu yuru ga nutsukamu story come on
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Are you ready for a few risks?
hey yo whoa tashou no risuku wa kakugo desho
You have to get up no matter how many times you fall. (Get it on!)
nanka korundatte tatsu get it on
It's not some conspiracy, just a paper-thin session
nare ai ja nai ze kami hitoe no sesshon
The pent up feelings turn into a crystal.
irikunda kanjou kidzukiageta kesshou
The rising cheers will become your courage.
wakiagaru kansei ga yuuki tonaru
So stand up now, no matter how much pain you feel.
tachiagareba ima ijou kurushimi tomonau
But in the end I'm sure you'll laugh.
soredemo saigo wa kitto warau
Everything will be swept away in victory and cheer.
subete sarau shouri to kansei
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
～♪
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
10 puppets vs 100 puppets
What's the matter...?
Aren't you going to attack?
どうした？ こないのか
The effects of the antidote
will last one more minute...
（サクラ）解毒効果は あと１分
Then...
（サソリ）ならば…
Water?
水… サクラ！ 離れろ！
Sakura! Get away!
あっ…
あっ！
うっ…
（サソリ）そらっ！
There!
いつまで 逃げ回ってるつもりだ
How long do you intend
to run about?
ハア ハア ハア…
（サクラ）あと… 20秒
Twenty seconds left.
そういうことなら…
If that's how it's going to be...
ハッ
おっ…
ううっ
（サクラ）あと15秒
Fifteen seconds... left...
（チヨ）大丈夫か！ サクラ！
Are you okay, Sakura?!
Die!
（サソリ）死ね！
チヨバア様！ ううっ…
Grandmother Chiyo!
あっ…
うっ…
（サクラ）解毒薬は効いてる
あとは 傷の痛みさえ耐えれば…
The antidote is working!
If I can just endure the pain...
フッ… ムダな努力だ
Your efforts are futile.
ああっ
Five seconds left!
（サクラ）あと５秒！
Four seconds.
４秒！
You little--!
このおお！
（チヨ）サクラか
Sakura?!
しゃーんなろー！
Shannaro!
（サクラ）３秒！
Three seconds.
Two!
２！
（サクラ）ハア ハア…
ハア… ううっ…
ハア ハア
We were able to beat him
（サクラ）ちょうど
解毒薬の持続時間内に 倒せた
exactly within the sustained duration
of the antidote...
ハア ハア フフッ…
We did it.
やりました
チヨバア様… やりましたよ！
Grandmother Chiyo, we did it!
サクラ お前…
Sakura...
You...
フフッ
（デイダラ）あのガキ…
すっかり おとなしくなったな…
That kid... has totally calmed down...
何をたくらんでる？ うん
What's he planning?
Kakashi-sensei!
Aren't you ready yet?!
（うずまきナルト）
カカシ先生 まだかよ
Hold your horses...
（はたけカカシ）そう焦るなって
俺は お前ほど
チャクラを持ってないからな
I don't have as much Chakra
as you, after all...
It's going to take time.
時間がかかるんだよ
（サクラ）んっ…
（サソリ）何をやったって…
What did you do?
ハッ…
That's right.
（チヨ）そうじゃなあ
やるのは これからじゃ
The fight is just beginning.
これは己で禁じた術
This is a Jutsu I myself sealed...
I didn't think I'd ever use it again...
２度と使うまいと思っておったが…
そうも いかんようじゃ
But it seems it won't work out
that way.
これで幕引きにしようぞ
Now let's put an end to this.
（サソリ）傀儡使いは…
It's said the ability of
a puppet master is measured
使える傀儡の数で
その者の能力が計れると言われるが
by the number of puppets they can use...
さすが ババアだ
I'd expect no less from you, Grandma.
す… すごい数　10体も？
Th-There's so many...
Ten of them.
チヨバア極意の指の数
Grandma Chiyo's secret
"Number of Fingers".
うわさには 聞いたが
I'd heard rumors about it...
それが城１つを
１人で落としたというカラクリ
The device you used to bring down
a castle by yourself...
白しろ秘技ひぎ･十機近松じゅっきちかまつの集
The Secret White Move:
Chikamatsu's 10 Puppets.
The ten masterpieces by Monzaemon,
傀儡の術
初代操演者 モンザエモンの十傑作
the first Puppeteer of
the Puppet Master Jutsu...
It's a great collection of puppets.
大した傀儡集だ
However...
だがな！
ハッ
I...
（サソリ）俺は
これで１国を落とした
used this to bring down a nation!
あっ…
（チヨ）こヤツ ここまで…
He's become... this powerful...
我ながら あきれる
I'm appalled at myself.
小娘と老いぼれ相手に
いつまでやってんだか
How long am I going to have to fight
a little girl and an old hag...?
最後のカラクリまで
見せることになるとはな
I never thought I'd have to
bring out my final device...
あっ…
Secret Red Move:
Performance of a Hundred Puppets...
（サソリ）赤あか秘技ひぎ･百機ひゃっきの操演
とくと見せてやる
I'll show you...
（チヨ）サクラ…
（サクラ）あっ…
Sakura...
お前は すでに解毒薬が切れとる
手を出すな
The effects of
your antidote have worn off.
Stay out of this.
うん？
You should already know...
もう分かってますよね　私の性格
my personality!
（チヨ）そうだな
性格も綱手つなで譲りだったな
That's right...
You've inherited
Tsunade's personality as well.
じゃがな これで終劇にするぞよ
覚悟はよいか
But let's make this the final act.
Are you ready?
（サクラ）はい！
Yes!
（サソリ）フッ
Here he comes!
（チヨ）くるぞよ
フン！
三宝吸潰さんぽうきゅうかい！
Three Treasures Suction Crush!
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
（サクラ）さすがに この数
With this many of them...
確実に数を減らすには
なんとか１対１に
The surefire way to lessen
the number
is to fight them one-on-one somehow...
（傀儡人形の動く音）
（サクラ）あっ！
よし！
All right!
There are too many of them!
（チヨ）数が多すぎる
（サクラ）くっ ハア ハア…
おっ くっ…
大丈夫か サクラ
Are you okay, Sakura?!
（サクラ）大丈夫です
I'm okay!
（チヨ）気を抜くでないぞ
Stay sharp!
Right!
（サクラ）はい！
（チヨ）サソリの傀儡は
確実に減っておる
There definitely aren't
as many of Sasori's puppets now...
じゃが ヤツの傀儡１体に対する集中力は
逆に上がっておるようじゃ
But conversely,
it looks like he's concentrating
more on each puppet now.
その上 解毒薬はあと１つ…
And on top of that,
we only have one antidote left.
わしかサクラのどちらかでも
傷つけば いきなりきつくなる
Things will get tough in a hurry
if either Sakura or I get wounded.
フッ…
（チヨ）はっ！
うわっ
（サクラ）あっ チヨバア様！
Grandmother Chiyo!
（チヨ）しまった
Oh no...!
大丈夫ですか？ チヨバア様
Are you okay, Grandmother Chiyo?
You don't need to worry about me!
わしの心配は無用じゃ
それより お主はサソリを狙え
More importantly, aim for Sasori.
ほかの傀儡は わしが抑える
I'll keep the other puppets in check!
はい！
Right!
（サクラ）ふん　あっ
サクラ！ それを使え！
Sakura, use that!
はっ！
ハア… ハア…
ハア ハア…
ここだあ！
Here!
（サソリ）おおっ…
（サクラ）ハア ハア…
ハア ハア… やった！
We did it!
ハア ハア ハア…
You can't move.
動けまい　その封印は
チャクラを完全に押さえ込むものじゃ
That seal completely
suppresses all Chakra.
もう… チャクラ糸は使えぬ
You can't use
your Chakra threads anymore.
終わりじゃよ サソリよ　ううっ…
It's over, Sasori...
（サクラ）
チヨバア様！ 早く解毒薬を！
Grandmother Chiyo!
Use the antidote quickly!
♪～
Just like always.
daitai itsumo doori ni
As I turn that corner.
sono kado wo magareba
I am lost in the waves of people.
hitonami ni magire komi
Melting, disappearing.
tokete kiete iku
I lose my way.
boku wa michi wo nakushi
I even completely lose my words.
kotoba suranaku shite shimau
But just one thing.
dakedo hitotsu dake wa
Remained, remained.
nokotteta nokotteta
Your voice.
kimi no koe ga
Your smiling faces, your angry faces, everything.
warau kao mo okaru kao mo subete
Keeps me walking on.
boku wo arukaseru
Surely, when I see the point where the clouds have broken.
kumo ga kireta saki wo mitara kitto nee
You know what I mean?
wakaru desho
nee wakaru desho
～♪
Next Episode
She was quick-witted
from the very beginning...
初めから頭のきれる子だったよ
And she was super cute...
それに ムチャクチャかわいかった
ええ あまりにも美しすぎました
僕の青春でした
She was way too beautiful!
She was my youth!
Despite her character,
she had her good points...
あれで 結構いいとこあったのよね
You're right...
そうだな
To think she'd pass away
so soon like this...
こんなに 早く逝っちまうなんて
Lee, cry into my arms!
リー 俺の胸で泣け
Guy-sensei!
ガイ先生！
Please watch over us...
俺たちを見守ってくれ
俺 絶対サクラちゃんのこと
忘れねえってばよ
I'll never forget about you, Sakura-chan!
ええい やめんか！
縁起でもない
Cut it out, all of you!
This is discouraging!
Next time: "Impossible Dream"
次回「叶わぬ夢」
Impossible Dream
Kunoichi Picture Book.
（サクラ）くノ一絵草紙(えぞうし)
（カカシ）今回の任務は
くノ一の調査だったな
Today's mission was kunoichi research,
wasn't it?
Report on the kunoichi
you have been assigned to.
各自が担当した
くノ一を報告してくれ
（ナルト･サクラ）了解！
— Roger!
Then I'll go first.
（サクラ）それじゃ 私から
I did my research on the sole female
in hot-blooded Team Guy.
担当は 熱血ガイ班の紅一点
あらゆる 忍具を使いこなす
テンテンさん
She's a master of various kinds of ninja tools. Tenten-san!
（カカシ）こゆ～い メンツの中の
清涼剤ってとこだな
She's a breath of fresh air in this group
of intense guys.
I researched the genjutsu expert,
Kurenai.
俺の担当は
幻術のエキスパート 紅くれないだ
（サクラ）へえ… 紅先生も
木ノ葉ベストを着ることあるんですね
Wow... So Kurenai-sensei also wears
the Leaf vest sometimes.
（ナルト）お～し
最後は俺の番だな
All right. Lastly, it's my turn.
（サクラ）…って これ
あんたの おいろけの術じゃない
Hey, isn't this your Sexy Jutsu?!
（ナルト）ダハハハ　なかなかの
ボンッ キュッ ボンッだろう
Pretty good waist,
hips and bust, huh?
さらに パワーアップした
新鋭の忍術 いくぜ！
And now for a powered-up,
new perverted ninjutsu!
（カカシ）おおっ
Ooh!
いいかげんにしろ！
Knock it off!
ボハハ～ン！
Yikes!
イタイ タイタ～イ
Owe!
This might be a new record...
（カカシ）こりゃ 新記録かな
（サクラ）ふんっ！
Humph!
（ナルト）あ…